LYRICS: Hey!! It's just like sweeet magic!! Aha!
LYRICS: Hi, it's me!
The one with that killer smile!
LYRICS: Stealing your gaze with a shocking style!
LYRICS: Smooth as ever, I escort you
LYRICS: And this voice, seducing you
LYRICS: Ah, come on, let's dance;
I'm aiming straight for your heart
LYRICS: I am your ace darlin'
LYRICS: Confidence? Yeah, I've got plenty
LYRICS: Please Please
LYRICS: Whisper just to me, call my name
LYRICS: You're too popular,
it drives me crazy and I'm not okay
LYRICS: But I'm sorry, losing's not my thing
LYRICS: Hey, girl
LYRICS: Look this way!
LYRICS: I see your smile, smile, smile,
I wanna make it all mine
LYRICS: Crash, crash, crash,
our special connection shines
LYRICS: Dance, dance,
our world is non-stop groovin'
LYRICS: I'll show you my perfect
A-side, side, side
LYRICS: And my private B-side, side, side;
I'll show you everything
LYRICS: So take my hand and let's roll
LYRICS: Sweet Sweet Sweet magic!!
LYRICS: Sweetie honey Sweetie honey
LYRICS: It's a spell that makes your heart race
LYRICS: We can't go back
LYRICS: You're falling in love with me, c'mon!
LYRICS: Sweetie honey
LYRICS: Sweet Sweet Sweet magic!!
UTAGE: There we go...
SONG: Washing everything away
SONG: Why couldn't I realize it back then?
SONG: The sky in a morning without you—
so carelessly clear
SONG: The RAIN won't stop
SONG: Under the sky, I start running
SONG: It's a new start - My days with you
SONG: I tuck them into my heart
and now I take a new step forward
SONG: Thank you for being there
SONG: RAIN—rain is falling
SIGN: Tamon's B-Side
UTAGE: Great work, Tamon-kun.
UTAGE: Thank you for the amazing
performance the other day.
UTAGE: Of course we're disappointed
that he couldn't take the center spot,
UTAGE: but...
UTAGE: Wow...
RANDO A: Hey, didn't Tamon-kun
seem different than usual?
RANDO B: I didn't know he could look like that.
RANDO A: Oh, man...
F/ACE: Thank you very much.
UTAGE: In the end, Tamon-kun gained
a ridiculous amount of fans.
UTAGE: Meanwhile,
UTAGE: Ouri-kun has established himself
as the eternal bridesmaid.
UTAGE: He struggled so much with that
heartbreak ballad in the beginning,
UTAGE: but he got it down perfectly by the end.
UTAGE: Tamon-kun is a god who evolves.
UTAGE: Pochi, wanna go on a walk?
UTAGE: There, there.
UTAGE: Isn't red a great color, Pochi?
UTAGE: Isn't Tamon-kun a god, Pochi?
UTAGE: What's the matter?
UTAGE: Hey!
UTAGE: Hey, where are you going, Pochi?!
UTAGE: We ended up at Tamon-kun's place...
UTAGE: Stay right here, Pochi!
UTAGE: Ta-mon-kun!
SIGN: This only took 15 seconds
UTAGE: Don't do anything rash!
TAMON: Kinoshita-san?!
UTAGE: What were you thinking?!
UTAGE: How could you put your precious body
in danger like that?!
TAMON: Please don't stop me!
TAMON: There's no reason for me to live anymore!
TAMON: It's a waste for someone like me
to be breathing everyone's air!
TAMON: The world is better off without me!
TAMON: If I disappear,
there won't be any more suffering!
TAMON: In my next life, I want to be a creature
that makes people happy just by existing!
TAMON: Like a hamster!
UTAGE: Please, calm down! It's quite
difficult being a hamster, too!
UTAGE: For example...
UTAGE: They have to spin their wheel...
UTAGE: Or struggle
to peel sunflower seeds!
TAMON: Oh, no! Is this world doomed?!
TAMON: It's hopeless!
MUSHROOM: Gloom!
UTAGE: Here you go.
TAMON: Thank you very much.
UTAGE: Have you calmed down a little now?
TAMON: Yes... I'm sorry.
UTAGE: Why would you do something like that?
UTAGE: Did you realize just how beautiful
your face is and lose your mind?
TAMON: Do I seem that merrily off my rocker?
UTAGE: Or you became afraid
of your beautiful voice...
TAMON: I wasn't able to be the center.
TAMON: Even though I received so much support,
I messed up the fifth round badly...
TAMON: But I wanted to sing
that song as the center.
UTAGE: Please don't be so depressed!
UTAGE: Your performance at N Station was amazing!
UTAGE: I'm sure a lot happened
until you got to that point.
UTAGE: But your performance on that stage
is burned into all of our brains.
UTAGE: So...
UTAGE: You'll still be smack dab in the center
of the hearts of us fans, Tamon-kun!
UTAGE: Not to mention, you've gained
an insane amount of fans since then,
UTAGE: and the old-school fans
are all happy that you've leveled up.
TAMON: And you, Kinoshita-san?
UTAGE: Huh?
UTAGE: Of course, that goes for me, too.
TAMON: You were cheering for Ouri-kun, too.
UTAGE: I'm sorry. Say that again?
TAMON: You two seemed really friendly...
TAMON: and before I knew it,
you were going to his house...
TAMON: So, um... I thought
you might be Ouri-kun's fan...
UTAGE: If you have something to say,
just spit it out, please.
UTAGE: Spit everything out right now
until you're satisfied,
UTAGE: and then smile again
as Hottiehara-san tomorrow.
UTAGE: Huh?
TAMON: Please don't go to Ouri-kun.
TAMON: Um, I'm sorry. I'm gonna say
something really weird right now.
UTAGE: I'm sorry?
TAMON: I don't really get it...
TAMON: But whenever I remember you
being near Ouri-kun,
TAMON: I just lose my will to live
for some reason...
UTAGE: Will... to live?
TAMON: This is affecting my work, so I've been
trying to figure out what to do...
UTAGE: G-Gloomyhara-san?
TAMON: This is the first time
I've ever felt like this...
UTAGE: Um...
TAMON: I'll keep doing my best!
TAMON: I'll even lick some boots and eat garbage.
UTAGE: Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What are you even say—
TAMON: I'll do anything if it makes you happy.
UTAGE: Gloomyhara-san's... being weird!
UTAGE: I can tell a lot's going through your mind
after the results the other day...
UTAGE: But you shouldn't say
those things, Tamon-kun!
UTAGE: He's probably just tired.
UTAGE: It's getting dark, so you
should return to your apartment.
UTAGE: Pochi's waiting for me downstairs,
so I need to head out, too.
TAMON: No matter how much of a failure I am,
TAMON: please just be my fan, Kinoshita-san.
TAMON: Otherwise, I'll...
TAMON: die.
UTAGE: Huh?
UTAGE: Wait, what?
Am I being threatened right now?
UTAGE: You don't have to ask.
I'll only ever be your fan.
UTAGE: Wait, is he holding me...
Am I just imagining it?
UTAGE: P-Please don't say you'll die so easily.
TAMON: You mean it?
UTAGE: I'm not imagining it at all!
UTAGE: Yes!
TAMON: I-I'm so sorry. I just got
really anxious all of a sudden.
TAMON: I didn't know what I'd do
if you changed oshis on me.
TAMON: I'm sorry.
UTAGE: The usual Gloomyhara-san.
UTAGE: And the usual Hottiehara-kun.
UTAGE: Then earlier... was that...
UTAGE: Tamon-kun's B-Side or something else?
TAMON: Oh, there's some tea left.
KEITO: What was that?
TAMON: Please wake up, Kinoshita-san!
TAMON: No! No!
TAMON: Kinoshita-san! Wake up!
TAMON: Please wake up!
TAMON: I'm so sorry! It's all my fault!
TAMON: What should I do?
UTAGE: Man, that startled me.
UTAGE: Gloomyhara-san's acting differently
than he usually does.
UTAGE: I guess being removed from
the center position really got to him.
UTAGE: That poor thing...
UTAGE: But I'll continue supporting you.
TAMON: Kinoshita-san!
TAMON: No! No!
TAMON: Please, wake up!
Please get a hold of yourself!
TAMON: Please! Please, wake up!
F/ACE: EYES ON YOU! We are F/ACE!
KEITO: Everyone! Thanks for supporting
F/ACE of F/ACE!
OURI: To everyone who's heading to work
and everyone staying at home,
OURI: thanks for watching!
TAMON: Yeah, thanks!
MC: Well, let's get started.
MC: Keito-kun got chosen as the center
for your new song, "RAIN."
MC: How do you feel right now?
KEITO: Yes, well, I had a tea stalk standing
in my tea just now, so I feel great.
MC: No, no, no. I mean how do you feel
about being the center?
KEITO: Oh, I see. Sorry about that.
NATSUKI: Jeez, get a grip already!
KEITO: I became the leader
because I'm the oldest,
KEITO: but starting today,
I'm also going to be the center.
KEITO: Of course, I'm a bit nervous,
KEITO: but I'll do my best and also
get advice from Tamon, too.
TAMON: Leave it to me!
MC: Tamon-kun, you've been switched
out of the center position, but...
TAMON: Honestly, I'm a bit disappointed,
TAMON: but any position is just as important.
TAMON: Also, Keito's a bit of an airhead usually,
TAMON: but he's super awesome
when he's singing, so I'm not worried.
KEITO: Thanks. I'll do my best not to get
leg cramps from being too nervous.
TAMON: And to all my girlfriends
that I love out there...
TAMON: I'll show you a new side of Tamon Fukuhara
that you've never seen before.
TAMON: You better look forward to it!
UTAGE: I wuv you.
MC: And that's all from the members of F/ACE!
F/ACE: Thank you very much!
NATSUKI: See you later!
SIGN: F/ACE's New Song "RAIN"
New Visual Just Revealed
MC: But wow, since the spacey
Keito-kun's now the center,
MC: I'm sure we'll be seeing
a new side of F/ACE.
MC: We're looking forward to
the release of their new song "RAIN"!
TAMON: We'll be going now!
NATSUKI/RINTARO: Thank you very much!
MALE STAFF A: F/ACE is super popular,
but they know their manners.
MALE STAFF B: Their leader Keito-kun
seems like a great guy, too!
MALE STAFF B: He's super popular.
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: Keito
SIGN: Home | Favorites
SIGN: Tama @tamachan_keito791...
He's so cute
#Keito-kun
SIGN: Keito 4 Life @life_k_face341
I'm relieved that he seems the
same even after becoming the center
#KeitoTachibana #Keito-kun
SIGN: Hoshityami @starhoshi1122
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah not enough Keito,
not enough Keito Hnnnnnnnnnnngggggghhhhh
#F/ACE #Keito-kun
SIGN: Keito Tachibana @keito_face_official
I'm F/ACE's silly center-slash-easygoing one.
I'm Keito Tachibana and it's a pleasure
#KeitoTachibana #F/ACE
KEITO: All according to plan.
KEITO: It's so nice that they're all fools
that're easy to manipulate.
OURI: Seriously, the difference
in your personas is so intense.
OURI: It creeps me out.
KEITO: You're one to talk.
OURI: Shut up. And don't mock our fans, trash.
KEITO: Goodness, you've got a bad mouth.
KEITO: I guess the other three
are headed elsewhere.
KEITO: Incidentally, Ouri.
KEITO: There's something I want to ask you.
OURI: You saying "Incidentally" pisses me off
for some reason, so nope.
OURI: I'll rip off your bangs.
KEITO: I saw Tamon with a mysterious girl.
KEITO: Do you know anything?
OURI: Wh-Who the hell cares about her?!
Why would I know?!
KEITO: So you do know.
KEITO: Is she the reason that Tamon's condition
has been so volatile lately?
OURI: There's no reason to hide it,
so I'll just tell you.
OURI: I'm gonna make that chick
fall for me someday.
OURI: The rest of this info doesn't matter.
OURI: She's an obsessive Tamon fangirl
and also his housekeeper.
KEITO: A... fangirl?
SIGN: Grand Maison Musashino
UTAGE: This is the first time in a while that
I'll be working at Gloomyhara-san's place.
UTAGE: Hopefully, he's gotten over his shock
at losing the competition for center.
TAMON: Hello.
UTAGE: Thank goodness.
It's his usual, barely audible voice.
It's the usual Gloomyhara-san.
UTAGE: Or not!
SIGN: Splash Splash Splash
SIGN: Wipe Wipe Wipe Wipe
SIGN: Voooooooor Vrrrrrrrrrrrrooor
UTAGE: I must repair the World Heritage artifact!
TAMON: I guess weak flour explodes...
TAMON: I guess the name was nothing
but a lie and a trap.
SIGN: Weak Flour
UTAGE: Um...
TAMON: Yes?
UTAGE: Is that a new outfit?!
TAMON: Ah! I'm sorry for trying to stay clean
despite being garbage!
UTAGE: Getting to be that close to you
and protect you...
UTAGE: The apron couldn't be more blessed!
UTAGE: But why are you wearing an apron?
TAMON: I was trying to make a cake.
SIGN: Weak Flour
UTAGE: A cake? Where did that come from?
TAMON: The competition for center
didn't go like I wanted,
TAMON: but you've been helping me out so much...
UTAGE: Huh?
TAMON: So I wanted to thank you somehow.
UTAGE: Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
You're baking me a cake?!
UTAGE: I couldn't possibly accept it!
UTAGE: Spend that time on your physical and
mental health and for your future instead!
TAMON: You're right.
MUSHROOMS: Gloom, gloom. Gloom.
UTAGE: Huh?
TAMON: No one would ever want to
eat something I've made.
TAMON: I should just sip on some muddy water
instead of baking a cake, huh?
UTAGE: If it's a cake that you've made,
Tamon-kun,
UTAGE: it would be Gâteau au chocolat
even if it was made of clay!
SIGN: gatoo chocolat
tAmoN fuKuhAra
MUSHROOMS: Gloom, gloom, gloom.
SIGN: Fresh Milk
SIGN: 100% Raw Milk
SIGN: Weak Flour
SIGN: Rich Butter
UTAGE: I've definitely made cakes for my oshi,
UTAGE: but to think the day would come
where the roles were reversed...
UTAGE: Life is full of surprises.
UTAGE: Are you sure you don't need any help?
TAMON: Yes.
TAMON: When I die, I want to make sure
I die without troubling anyone.
UTAGE: Please don't risk your life making a cake!
TAMON: Okay, I've learned the steps.
UTAGE: Yes. First, you need to sift
the weak flour through a sifter.
TAMON: Ah...
UTAGE: He's terrible at this.
UTAGE: No wonder a dust explosion
occurred earlier.
UTAGE: Next, he needs to melt
the butter in hot water.
UTAGE: And he put it directly into the hot water!
TAMON: It's hot!
UTAGE: I won't help,
but can I watch you from here?
UTAGE: I love watching cakes being made.
TAMON: R-Really?
UTAGE: Yes!
UTAGE: This takes me back to when I made
a birthday cake for Tamon-kun.
SIGN: June 12
Tamon Fukuhara's Birthday Celebration
UTAGE: It turned out pretty well
if I do say so myself.
SIGN: An Otaku's
SIGN: Biggest Event
SIGN: Unconditional Love
for Tamon Fukuhara!!
SIGN: A Birthday Party Without the Actual Birthday Boy
UTAGE: Baking cakes is fun, isn't it?
TAMON: On my birthday, my fans make me cakes.
TAMON: It's not like I can actually eat those,
TAMON: but they make me happy.
TAMON: Cakes really are special.
UTAGE: And then all of his followers cried!
UTAGE: All of your fans around the world
would sob if they heard you say that.
UTAGE: We're all making them
filled with our love after all.
TAMON: Love...
TAMON: Okay, I'll put all of my feelings
into making this, too.
TAMON: I hope that Kinoshita-san will be
able to deliciously enjoy this cake.
UTAGE: He's too friggin' cute!
TAMON: I hope that Kinoshita-san will
continue coming over forever.
UTAGE: You're giving me that privilege?!
TAMON: I hope that Kinoshita-san never hates me.
UTAGE: That won't happen—
TAMON: And never betrays me.
UTAGE: Huh...?
TAMON: Or cheats on me.
TAMON: May she never show any interest in
the rest of humanity for all her life.
TAMON: I'm going to make this delicious.
MUSHROOMS: Gloom, gloom, gloom, gloom...
UTAGE: I thought he was better now,
but he's still acting weird.
TAMON: No matter how much of a failure I am,
TAMON: please just be my fan, Kinoshita-san.
UTAGE: Does anyone say all that
to their housekeeper?
UTAGE: I mean, I told him that
I'd only ever be his fan, but...
UTAGE: I-It's done!
SIGN: Kill... me...
SIGN: Kinoshita-san
CAKE: Kill... me... Kill... me...
UTAGE: Wow! A homemade cake that my oshi made!
CAKE: I'm going to freeze it
and make it my gravestone!
TAMON: No...
TAMON: Please, eat it.
TAMON: I even bought some delicious
Poca Cola to go with it.
UTAGE: I'm sorry.
UTAGE: But I'm currently working, so...
UTAGE: I'll humbly accept the thought, though.
UTAGE: Oh, no. I made Tamon-kun sad.
UTAGE: But I just can't...
UTAGE: I'll go clean the bathroom!
UTAGE: Huh?
TAMON: Eat it.
TAMON: Even just a bite.
TAMON: Come on. Please?
TAMON: Open up.
TAMON: Accept it... All of my love.
UTAGE: Tamon-kun, no...
UTAGE: We mustn't...
UTAGE: It has no taste.
UTAGE: W-Well,
UTAGE: it's not unusual to have some tea
and snacks after finishing work,
UTAGE: so a little won't hurt...
UTAGE: Okay, I'm done cleaning,
so I'll have some.
UTAGE: This is the first time in my life
UTAGE: that someone gifted me a whole cake
on a completely random day.
UTAGE: It's delicious.
MUSHROOMS: Gloomy, gloom... Gloomy, gloom...
UTAGE: I had been treating Tamon-kun like
a cute little needy puppy...
UTAGE: But then he got all weird to the point
UTAGE: that I'm getting worried that
he might not even be from this planet.
TAMON: Have some cola, too.
UTAGE: Th-Thank you very much.
UTAGE: He... totally flipped his switch
on purpose earlier, didn't he?
TAMON: Let's eat.
UTAGE: He did that knowing full well
that would stop me, didn't he?
UTAGE: Looking back on it now,
this isn't the first time it happened.
UTAGE: Lately, it's almost been normal
to be so close to him,
UTAGE: but Gloomyhara-san is a super idol who
puts people everywhere under his spell.
UTAGE: And he's playing a character
he created to do just that.
UTAGE: Meaning, finessing one fangirl
would be nothing to him.
SIGN: Kinoshita-san
UTAGE: And he definitely finessed me...
This is dangerous.
UTAGE: I should get going.
TAMON: What? Already?
UTAGE: This fanservice is so extreme...
UTAGE: He's basically devaluing
himself as an idol.
UTAGE: I can't let this escalate any further.
UTAGE: I'll take the rest home with me.
Could I borrow an ice pack?
TAMON: Oh... sure.
TAMON: I need to keep my distance.
TAMON: Being overprotective isn't always love.
TAMON: I need him to be able to
survive on his own.
TAMON: Kinoshita-san, you've got some
frosting on your face.
UTAGE: Huh?
TAMON: Right here.
UTAGE: It's fine! Please stay back!
UTAGE: You needn't dirty your hands
over something like this!
TAMON: You don't need to hold back.
UTAGE: Huh?
TAMON: We're closer than that, aren't we, Utage?
UTAGE: He...
UTAGE: He did it again!
UTAGE: This fanservice is too extreme!
TAMON: I'm sorry. I just reacted.
TAMON: But I figured you'd be
okay with it, Kinoshita-san.
SIGN: Kinoshita
UTAGE: Huh?
UTAGE: He's sulky, gloomy, and always
sensitive to others' moods.
UTAGE: That's exactly what
makes him a sharpshooter...
SIGN: Kinoshita-san
TAMON: Because...
TAMON: You think I'm hot.
UTAGE: Tamon-kun's... always been like that.
Credits: \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hTranslation:
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSubtitle Timing:
Editing and Typesetting:
Credits: Michelle Tymon
\h\hMariana Martinez
Ashley Barboza
Credits: \h\h\h\h\hQuality Control:
Translation Check:
Credits: Alicia Ashby
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSriram Gurunathan
LYRICS: Uh huh...
LYRICS: Na na na...
LYRICS: I wonder what the world
would look like without you
LYRICS: When I look back,
you've always been by my side
LYRICS: Teaching me what "warmth"
and "happiness" feel like
LYRICS: A speedboat sails across the endless skies
LYRICS: An unwavering course,
a straight shot down the middle
LYRICS: An unbreakable red balloon
found nowhere else
LYRICS: Is this "fate"? Or just a "coincidence"?
LYRICS: Like a wilted flower coming back to life
LYRICS: A light that shines
LYRICS: Through the impossibly dark night
LYRICS: (Light of your soul)
LYRICS: I wanted to grasp it
LYRICS: (I love you so)
LYRICS: So I strived for it
LYRICS: Wanna keep going, wanna keep growing
LYRICS: Bringing our flowers and dreams
into full bloom